Greenbaum, Marcia Papers 6091
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitration Documents: 1984 U.S. Postal Service-- 1985 Corando. (Box 31)
  - Beck & Beck and ARB 85 Granite Cutters Union Local 219, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - BD. Of Regents, Framingham St. Coll. And ARB 85 M.T.A. Science Workload, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Bristol Board of Education and AAA #1239-0057-85 ARB 85 Bristol Federation of Teachers, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Brookline School Committee and Mediation 1985 Brookline Edj cators' Assn. (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Carando Inc. and AAA #1230-0405-84 ARB 85 U.F.C.W., Loc. 371 R. Bergstrom, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    Contains 2 photographs
- Arbitration Documents: 1985 Champlain Cable-- Plymouth Inc./Carver School. (Box 32)
  - Champlain Cable Co. and FMCS #85K/11017 ARB 85 Teamsters Local 597 Discharge, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Chandler Evans Inc. and AAA #1230-0073-85 ARB 85 U.A.W.Unity Lodge #405, 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Elliott Stevedoring Co. and AAA #1130-1274-85 ARB 85 U.F.C.W. Local 15, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Essex Company Newspapers and AAA #1130-0291-85 ARB 85 No. Shore Media Union # 50, 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Fafnir Bearing Co. ARB 85 and #84-307 U.A.W. Local 133 (Folder 1 of 2), 1985 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Fafnir Bearing Co. ARB 85 and #84-307 U.A.W. Local 133 (Folder 2 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - WM. Fillenes & Sons Co. and AAA #1130-1868-85 ARB 85 UFCW, Local 1445 M. Samples, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - The Gorton Group and FMCS #85K/12997 ARB 85 U.F.C.W. Local 15, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - The Gorton Group and ARB 85 Fireman & Oilers, Local 3, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - ITT Royal Electric Div. and AAA #1130-0051-85 ARB 85 I.B.E.W. Local 1196 (Folder 1 of 2), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - ITT Royal Electric Div. and AAA #1130-0051-85 ARB 85 I.B.E.W. Local 1196 (Folder 2 of 2), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - F.R. Lepage Bakery and FMCS #84K/2509 ARB 85 Teamsters, Local 440 Discharge, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Market Forge Co. and AAA #1130-2165-84 ARB 85 USWA Jordan suspension, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Mass. Electric Co. and BWUNE, Local 330 ARB 85, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Milliken Tomlinson Co. and FMCS #85K/19527 ARB 85 Teamsters Local 340 R. Duarte, 1980-1985 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Narragansett Electric Co. and S.Zaremba ARB 85 B.U.W.N.E. Local 310, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - New England Power Service and ARB 85 BUWNE, Local 317 D. Blatchford, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - New England Power Service and #85-4, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11 & 12 U.W.U.A. Local 464 ARB 85, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - New England Powe Service Co. and ARB 85 BUWNE Local 345 P.Lovejoy, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - New Haven Board of Education and AAA #1239-0014-85 ARB 85 New Haven FEDN. Of Teachers, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - New York Telephone Co. and #A-84-97 ARB 85 C.W.A. Local 1101 Overtime Gr., 1985 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Noranda Metals Inc. and AAA #1230-0052-85 ARB 85 UAW, Local 376 Fleming Susp., 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - O ' Donnell-USEN Co. ARB 85 and U.F.C.W. Local 15, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Parker Brothers and FMCS #85K/12072 ARB 85 Firemen & Oilers, Local 3 (Folder 1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Parker Brothers and FMCS #85K/12072 ARB 85 Firemen & Oilers, Local 3 (Folder 2 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - S.S. Pierce Co. and ARB 85 Teamsters #829 Discharge, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Plymouth-Carver School Committee and AAA #1139-1900-84 ARB 85 Plymouth-Carver ED. Association (Folder 1 of 2), 1985 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Plymouth-Carver School Committee and AAA #1139-1900-84 ARB 85 Plymouth-Carver ED. Association (Folder 1 of 2), 1985 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Arbitration Documents: 1985 Plymouth Inc./Carver-- Upton, Town of. (Box 33)
  - Plymouth-Carver School Comms. And AAA #1139-1900-84 ARB 85 Plymouth-Carver ED. Assn. File #2 (Folder 1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Plymouth-Carver School Comms. And AAA #1139-1900-84 ARB 85 Plymouth-Carver ED. Assn. File #2 (Folder 2 of 2), 1970-1984 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Purity Supreme Supermarkets and Teamsters, Local 829 (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Purity Supreme Supermarkets and Teamsters, Local 829 (Folder 2 of 2), 1981-1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - City of Providence and AAA #1139-1387-85 ARB 85 P.S.E. Local 1033 A.Patton, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Providence Housing Authority and AAA #1139-1645-85 ARB 85 R.I.L.D.C. Local 1217 L. Lovelace, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Raytheon Company and AAA #1130-2003-84 ARB 85 Raytheon Guards Assn. B. Cooper, 1975-1985 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - State of Rhode Island and AAA #1139-0457-84 ARB 85 AFSCME Locals 1350 &2874 Goldman, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Rounder Records and FMCS #85K/11264 ARB 85 SEIU Local 925 Discharge (Folder 1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Rounder Records and FMCS #85K/11264 ARB 85 SEIU Local 925 Discharge (Folder 2 of 2), 1985 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Salem Evening News and Lynn Typog. Union No. 120, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Shaw's Supermarket, Inc. and AAA #1130-1192-84 ARB 85 Ind. Food Handlers C. Sullivan, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. and AAA #1130-0845-85 ARB 85 Ind. Food Handlers Overtime Rel, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Stowe, VT. BD. Of School Dirs. And ARB 85 Stowe Teachers Assn., 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 85 and N1C-1M-D 25489 K. Banks A.P.W.U., 1983-1985 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Posta Service ARB 85 and N1C-1M-D 28091 M. Conklin A.P.W.U. 28090, 1983-1985 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 85 and N1C-1A-D 26214 R. Gadsden A.P.W.U., 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 85 and N1C-1M-D 29914 & 29915 A.P.W.U. T. Latham, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 85 and N1C-1M-D 28092 R. Marinacci A.P.W.U. 27877, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 85 and N1C-1M-D 36135 R. Soler A.P.W.U., 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Unheard Postal Service Cases 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Town of Upton and JLMC 84-43P Spec. Master M.C.O.P. Local 162, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - In the Mater of: Town of Upton and Upton Police Association Local 162, MCOP, AFL-CIO (Folder 1 of 2), 1984 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - In the Mater of: Town of Upton and Upton Police Association Local 162, MCOP, AFL-CIO (Folder 2 of 2), 1984 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Arbitration Documents: 1985 Windham Comm.-- 1986 Kraft Inc.. (Box 34)
  - Windham Comm. Memorial Hospital and AAA #1230-0278-85 ARB 85 C.S.F.T. /WCMH Fedn. Of Nurses, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Wrightson Typographers and Expedited ARB 1985 Boston Typo. Union Local 13 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Yale University and AAA #1230-0261-85 ARB 85 Fedn. Of Univ. EES. Local 34 (Folder 1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Yale University and AAA #1230-0261-85 ARB 85 Fedn. Of Univ. EES. Local 34 (Folder 1 of 2), 1986 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - American Can Co.-Fitchburg and AAA #1130-1557-86 ARB 86 IUE, #210 GR #25-85 (Tape Mach), 1986 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Baron-Abramson ARB 86 and AAA #1130-2069-86 ILGWU GR, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Barrington School Committee and AAA #1139-1883-85 ARB 86 Barrington Teachers Association (Folder 1 of 2), 1986 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Barrington School Committee and AAA #1139-1883-85 ARB 86 Barrington Teachers Association (Folder 2 of 2), 1982-1986 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Bay State Bus Corp. ARB 86 and AAA #1130-1716-86 ATU Local #1547, 1985-1987 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Briarcliff Health Care Facility and AAA #1130-0205-86 ARB 86 R.I. Workers Union, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Cranston School Committee and AAA #1139-0207-86 ARB 86 Cranston Teachers Alliance, 1980-1986 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Chandler Evans Inc. and AAA #1230-0250-86 ARB 86 UAW, Local 405 Discharge, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Chase & Sons, Inc. and AAA #1130-1394-86 ARB 86 URW, Local 562, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - University of Connecticut and Mediation 86 Univ. Prof. Employees Assn., 1986 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Fleet Service and FMCS #86K/10238 ARB 86 Teamsters, Local 559, 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Georgia, VT. Board of Education and ARB 1986 Georgia Teachers' EDN. Assn, VTA, 1981-1987 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Groton-Dunstable School Committee and AAA #1139-1553-86 ARB 86 Groton-Dunstable Educators Assoc., 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Hartford Board of Education and AAA #1239-0463-85 ARB 85 Hartford Federation of Teachers, 1986-1989 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Hartford Board of Education and AAA #1239-0202-86 ARB 86 Hartford Federation of Teachers, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Harvard University and AAA #1130-1285-86 ARB 86 HRIEB #25, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - ICI Americas, Inc. and FMCS #86K/03895 ARB 86 I.C.W.U. Local 779, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - ITT World Communications, Inc. and AAA #1330-0867-86 ARN86 CWA GR, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Johnston School Committee and AAA #1139-1386-86 ARB 86 Johnston Federation of Teachers, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Kraft, Inc. and AAA #1130-1464-86 ARB 86 Teamsters Local #380, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Arbitration Documents: 1986 Leominster Hospital-- Yale University. (Box 35)
  - Leominster Hospital and AAA #1130-0492-86 SEIU, Local 285, 1985-1987 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Longmeadow School Committee and AAA #1139-0948-86 ARB 86 Longmeadow Education Assn., 1986 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - City of Lynn and ARB 86 Lynn Police Association, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Marble Motor Co. and FMCS# 86K/13439 ARB 86 Teamsters, Local 437, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Mass. BD. Of Community Colleges Massasoit Com. Coll. / Bunker Hill and AAA #1139-01121-86 ARB 86 AFSCME #93 GR, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Mass BD. Of Trustees of State Colleges (Salem State) and Mass. Teachers Assoc. ARB 86, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Mass. Board of Regents of High Education, Westfield State Coll. MTA/NEA ARB 86, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts Electric Co. and BUWNE, Local 330 ARB 86, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - New York Telephone and A-86-28/1-86-91 ARB 86 CWA Local 1101, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Oakwood Metal and FMCS #86K/09475 ARB 86 UAW, Local 163, 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Penn Central Telecomm. Co. ARB 86 and FMCS #86K/31235 IUE, Local 222 GR# 1-86 Discipline, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - City of Providence and AAA #1139-1996-85 ARB 86 R.I. Laborers, Local 1033, 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - City of Quincy and ARB 83 Quincy Police, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Quincy City Hospital ARB 86 and AAA #1139-1781-85 SEIU, Local 285 GR: Deny Benefit, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Rest Haven Nursing Home and AAA #1130-1932-85 ARB 86 NEHCE, District 1199, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - State of Rhode Island and AAA #1139-0572-86 ARB 86 AFSCME, Council 94 Ladd G-674, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Roger Williams College ARB 86 and NEA Representing Physical Plant & Clerical Unions, 1985-1987 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Salem News Publishing Co. and Boston Mailers' Union # 1, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Stop & Shop Supermarket Co. and AAA #1230-0354-85 ARB 86 UFCW, Local 371, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1N-1A-D 2504 N.A.L.C., 1983-1986 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Van Buren Education ASSN. and AAA #1139-0876-86 ARB 86 Maine Teachers ASSN., 1986 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Wellesley College and AAA #1130-0230-86 ARB 86 W.C. Campus Police ASSN., 1986 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Westboro School Committee and AAA #1139-1012-86 ARB 86 Westboro Teachers Association, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Western Mass. Electric and AAA #1130-2099-85 ARB 86 IBEW, Local 455 Gr. P6, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Western Mass. Electric Co. and AAA #1130-0561-86 ARB 86 IBEW Local #455, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - WGGB-TV & WHYN Stations Corp. and FMCS #86K/ 04291 ARB 86 NABET Gr. G-85-20, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Andrew Wilson Co. and AAA # 1130-0325-86 ARB 86 USWA, Local 3409, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Woonsocket School Committee and AAA #1139-1100-86 ARB 86 Woonsocket Teachers Guild, 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Yale University and ARB 86 F.U.E., Local 35 1982-8868, 1984-1986 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Arbitration Documents: 1987 Agawam School-- New Can Co.. (Box 36)
  - AGAWAM School Committee FF 87 and MBC&A #PS-3-1987 AGAWAm Education Assoc/MTA (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - ARKWRIGHT Finishing, Div. of United MLM, Inc. and AA # 1130-2384-86 ARB 87 So. New England Jt. Bd., 1987 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Beloit Copr., Jones Division and AAA 1130-0154-87 ARB 87 UE.#212 (GR), 1987 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Boston Edison Company ARB. 1987 and AAA #1130-1672-87 Cianton UTIL. Workers Un., Local #387 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Brockton School Committee ARB 87 and AAA #1139-2283-86 Brockton Education Assoc., 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Brockway- Smith Co. and AAA #1130-0077-87 ARB 87 Teamsters Local # 379, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Charlesgate Nursing Center and AAA #113-0181-87 ARB 87 Local 76/ RI Workers Union, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Cranston, RH. IS. School Committee and AAA #1139-0195-87 ARB 1987 Cranston Teachers Alliance (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Eastern Air Lines, Inc. ARB 87 and (L. Davis) 735-86 Transport Workers Union Local 553, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Federal Aviation ADMN. NE Region and Gr. #(P) ANE-86-27-ZBW-2 Profl. Airways Sys. Specialists, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - USA Dept. of Trans. Fed. Aviation Admin. In the Matter of: Fed. Aviation Admin., 1987 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Fine Host Inc. ARB 1987 and FMCS # 87-17936 HERE, Local 217 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Town of Framinghmam FF 87 and JLMC-86-12F Teamsters Local 122, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Harvard University ARB 87 and #1130-2374-86 AAA HRIE&BU #26 Seniority, 1982-1987 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - L.& J. Corrugated Box Corp. and AAA #1130-0668-87 ARB United Paperworkers Int. #1407, 1985-1989 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - James River Corp. ARB 87 and AAA #1130-0777-87 UPIU # 80 (FR 169-86, 176-86, 186-86), 1987 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Kraft Incorporated and AAA #1130-1025-87 ARB INTL. BRO. of Teamsters, Locl, 380, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Kraft, Inc. Schippers ARB 1987 and AAA #1130-1839-87 Teamsters, CWHA, Local #380, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Linweave, Inc. ARB 198 and AAA #1130-1122-87 Thyer United Paperworkers, Local #1, 1983-1987 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - City of Lynn Direct ARB 87 and RE: Court Minimums Lynn Police Association, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - State of Maine and AAA #1139-0125-87 ARB 87 Maine State EMP. ASSN, 1986-1989 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Mass. Board of Regents of Higher Education, Bridgewater State College and M.T.A. ARB 87, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Mass. Board of Regents of Higher Educ. Fitchburg State College MTA Prof. J. Clark ARB 87, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - M.I.T. and AAA #1130-0040-87 R.D.T.E.U., 1987 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Narragansett Electric Co. NEPSCO and ARB 1987 Direct Bro. of Util Workers of NE, #310 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Narragansett Electric Co. 1987 and Termination of E. Donnell B.U.W.N.E., Local #310 Direct, 1982-1987 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - 1982-1987 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - City of Nashua, NH ARB 87 and AAA #1139-1968-86 Nashua Fire Fighters Local 789, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - New Can Company and AAA #1130-0118-87 ARB 1987 RWDSU, Local #588 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Arbitration Documents: 1987 New England Power-- Telco of New England. (Box 37)
  - New England Power Service Co. ARB 87 and GR. #86-8, 12 and 14 United Utility Workers, Loc. # 464, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - North Atlantic Distribution, Inc. and AAA 1130-0151-87 ARB 87 I.L.A., Local 1996-1, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - American Arbitration Association Hearing, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - OMNI- Biltmore Hotel and AAA #1130-1466-87 ARB H.E.R.E.B.U. Local #217, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Package Machinery and AAA #11E 34-0001-87 ARB 87 IUE Local #220, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Package Machinery Corp. ARB 1987 and AAA #11E34 0-0003-87 INTL. UN. Of Electrical, Loc. #220 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - City of Providence, RI ARB 87 and AAA #1139-1800-87 RI Laborers Dist. Council, L. 1033, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - City of Providence and AAA #1139-2138-87 ARB 87 Public Service EMP. Local 1033, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - City of Quincy ARB 87 and AAA #1139-1323-87 JOI Quincy Police Betterment ASSN., 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Quincy School Committee 1987 and Mediation Quincy Education Association, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Quincy School Committee and AAA #1139-0314-87 ARB 87 Quincy EDUC. ASSN. (GR.E. Silverio), 1987 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Raynham School Committee 1987 and MBC& A Mediation Raynham Teachers ASSN., 1988 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Ritz Carlton ARB 1987 and AAA #1130-1467-87 H.E.R.E.I.U., 1988 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Robbins Company ARB and AAA #1130-1556-87 ARB INTL. ASSN. of Machinists wk ass, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - SACO Defense Systems ARB 88 3case and FMCS #87-11322, 23, 13310 ME. Jt. BD., ACTWU, Loc. 406, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Sears, Roebuck & CO. ARB 87 and Teamsters, Local 25, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Somerville School Committee and AAA #1139-0735-87 ARB Somerville Administrators Assn., 1988 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Somerville School Comm. And AAA 1139-0806-87 Arb. 87 Somerville Teachers Assn, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Springfield School Committee and AAA #1139-0229-87 ARB 87 Springfield Education ASSN KIAH, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Memorandum To Design Division Employees in the Bargaining Unit, 1977-1987 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts Amer. Arbitration Assoc. in the matter between: Assoc. of Engineers, Architects, and Draftsmen, Local # 105 and Stone & Webster Engineering Corp., 1987 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Stone & Webster Engineering Corp. and AAA 1130-0476-87 ARB 87 ASSN. ENG., ARCH., DRFTSMN, Loc.. 105, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Stone & Webster Engineering Corp. and AAA #1130-1036-87 ARB ASSN. OF ENGRS. ARCH. DR. LOC. #105, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Telco of N.E. FEDL Credit Union and AAA #1130-0720-87 ARB I.B. of Teamsters, Local #340, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Arbitration Documents: 1987 Warwick School-- Boston Edison Co.. (Box 38)
  - Warwick School Committee ARB 87 and AAA # 1139-0596-87 Warwick Teachers Union Gr #799, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Warwick School Committee and AAA #1139-0800-87 ARB Warwick Teachers Union GR. #801, 1986-1988 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Warwick School Committee ARB87 and AAA #1139-2059-86 Warwick Teachers Union, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Wellesley College and AAA #1130-1285-87 Zonak I.M.S.E.U. suspension, 1987-1988 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - WGBH Education Foundation and A.E.E.F. direct ARB87 Grievance, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Acton Boxborough School Comm. ARB and AAA #1139-1037- 87 1988 AFSMCE, Council #93, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - ADT CO. ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-1348-88 Mullan INTL. UN. OF. ELECT., Local #239, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Alaska Air Lines Pilots 1988 Med and ALPA Merger Mediation JedAmerica Pilots (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - AMGRAPH Packaging Inc. ARB 1988 and AAA #1230-0230-88 Discrimn. Greater Northeastern JT.. BD. ACTWU, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Arkwright, ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-0856-88 Fernande GR> Northeastern JT. BD. ACTWU, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Amer.Arbitration Assoc. In the Matter of Arbitration Between: Greater Northeastern Joint Board and Arkwright, Incorporated, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Arrows Farm, Inc. ARB 1988 and FMCS #88-07772 D. URAV Teamsters, Local 25, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Ashland, ME. School Board 1988 and MSAD #32 M. Ashby Direct Ashland Area Teachers ASSN., 1989 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - AT-A-Glance DIV. of Keith-Clarke and AAA #1130-0826-88 ARB United Paperworkers, Loc. 882, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Bailey Corporation ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-2294-87 Hardy United Auto Workers, Loc. 1913 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Beloit Corporation ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-2425-87 bonus United Electrical, Loc. #121 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - BOISE Cascade Paper CO. ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-1621-87 UPIU, Loc. #900 Gr. 3219 Drug test, 1987-1988 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Amer. Arbit. Assoc. Local 900, United Paperworkers International Union V. Boise Cascade Corporation AAA # 1130-1621-87, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Boston Edison Company ARB 88 and Direct P&M Gr, #3656 UWUA, Local #369, 1987-1988 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Boston Edison Company ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-1167-88 Utility Workers U.A., Loc. 369 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Boston Edison Company ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-1466-88 Utility Workers UN. OF AM., L.369 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Boston Edison Company ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-1932-87 Utility Workers UN. OF AM, #387 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Boston Edison Company ARB 1988 AAA #1130-1132-88 Discharge Utility Workers UN. AM, Loc. #369, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Amer. Arbit. Assoc. Between Boston Edison Company -and- Local 369, Utility Workers Union of America AFL-CIO, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Boston Edison Co. ARBdirect 1988 and P& M Gr. # 3674 OCI Mtcemar Utility Workers UN. Of Amer. # 369, 1988- 1989 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Arbitration Documents: 1988 Boston Gear -- James River Corp.. (Box 39)
  - Arbitration Between Boston Edison Company -and- Local 369, Utility Workers Union of America AFL-CIO, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Boston Gear Incom Intl. 1988 and Direct ARB United Steelworkers, Local # 4335 (Folder 1 of 2), 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Boston Gear Incom Intl. 1988 and Direct ARB United Steelworkers, Local # 4335 (Folder 2 of 2), 1990 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Boston University ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-0322-88 Fitzpatric Service EES Intl. Union, Loc. #254, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Amer. Arbit. Assoc. Service Employees International Union, Local 254 and Boston University, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Bridgeport, CT. BD. Of ED. 1988 and AAA #1239-0221-88 Bridgeport Teachers Assn., 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Brookline, MA, School Committee and AAA #1139-2568-87 ARB 88 Brookline Education ASSNN. Walker, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Building Technology Engineering and AAA #1130-2288-87 ARB 88 IBFO, Local # 3 Whalen & Tansevich, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - City of Cambridge, MA ARB 1988 and Discharge Direct Cambridge Police ASSN. KLODNER, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Certificate- Armos Eyal, RPR Notary Public (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Carando, Inc. ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-0501-88 Ferreira United Food & Commercial W.K #371 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Chandler Evans Corp. ARB 1988 and AAA #1230-0299-88 United Auto Workers, Local #405, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Chandler Evans Corp. ARB 1988 and AAA #1230-0299-88 United Auto Workers, Local # 405 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Charlesgate Nursing Center ARB and AAA #1130-1131-88 DeVerte RI Workers Union, Local #76, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Continental Baking Company ARB and AAA #1130-1592-88 Breaks Bakery Workers, Local #348, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - CPM, Inc. E. Rygate, VT ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-2581-87 United Paperworkers, Loc. #499 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Cranston, RI School Committee and AAA #1139-0400-88 ARB Cranston Teachers Alliance, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Daniel Marr & Son Co. ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-0961-88 Hoist IronWorkers, Local #7 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Dighton - Rehoboth Regional S.C. and AAA #1139-2411-87 ARB Dighton-Rehoboth Regnl Teachers, 1986-1989 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Distribution & Auto Service, Inc. and AAA #1130-0696-88 job bid Intl. Longshoremen Assn. L. 1996, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Eastern Air Lines, Inc. ARB 1988 and NMB Expedited Arbitration Transport Workers UN., Loc. 553 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Filene' Basement ARB 1988 and AAA #1130-2135-87 UFCW, Local #144 R. College bid, 1983-1987 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Fox Press Inc. ARB 1988 and FMCS 88-24157 Pay at Termn GCIU, Local 264-M, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 23)